My work can, of course, take me away
from my home and my kids. Whatever it is
that I'm doing,
>> [music]
>> it has to be worth it.
Because I'm I'm missing time away from
them, watching them grow, having them
ask me questions. This morning, Titan
saw me getting ready for this. He's
like, "Where are you going?" And I was
like, "I'm not going anywhere." Like I
know that this space and stage of his
life, he just
>> [music]
>> wants me close. And whatever it is that
I'm doing is
got to It means something to me. And I
told him that and I was like, "If I'm
leaving or going somewhere, it's because
it really means a lot to me." I was
like, "And I don't want to leave you."
And he goes, "Okay." You got to just
talk to them like they're human.
>> [music]
>> I don't baby my boys. I'm completely
obsessed with them, so I just love them
and kiss on them all day. So, there's
never [music]
a moment where they don't feel like I
love them, even when [music] there is
some sort of challenge, you know what I
mean? Or it's figuring [music] out, you
know, you you feel like you have a
bigger voice than you're 11, but you
don't use that tone of voice with me.
You know what I mean? That kind of
thing. Like we I talk to Titan [music]
and Noah like that, you know? I'm like,
"I don't like the way you said that to
me. I wouldn't say that to you like
that, so don't say that to me like
that." And then it's over. I wish
someone would have told me, "Make it
quick, you know, when you're correcting
something, and move on." And I wish
someone [music] would have said,
"Let your yes be a yes and your no be a
no."
And immediately when something happens,
like [music] nip it in the bud. Oh.
Oh, and boundaries. Oh.